(playful music)
♪ This is a man's world ♪
♪ But it wouldn't be nothing ♪
♪ Nothing without
a woman or a girl ♪
♪ You see, man made the cars
to take us over the road ♪
♪ Man made the train to
carry the heavy load ♪
♪ Man made the electric light
to take us out of the dark ♪
♪ Man made the boat for the
water, like Noah made the ark ♪
♪ This is a man's,
man's, man's world ♪
♪ But it wouldn't be nothing ♪
♪ Nothing without
a woman or a girl ♪
♪ Man thinks about our
little bitty baby girls ♪
♪ And our baby boys ♪
♪ Man made them happy,
'cause man made them toys ♪
♪ And after man make
everything, everything he can ♪
♪ You know that man makes
money, to buy from other man ♪
♪ This is a man's world ♪
♪ But it wouldn't be
nothing, nothing ♪
♪ Not one little thing,
without a woman or a girl ♪
♪ He's lost in the wilderness ♪
♪ He's lost in bitterness ♪
♪ He's lost, lost ♪